I think
we're becoming more and more
like a team.
Yes.
I think so too.
Right.
Should we change the group name?
The previous group name
was "share blessings, leave when in trouble".
That's too superficial.
How about "Five blessings in the door"?
What do you think?
That's even worse.
Yibei will win!
How about that?
Straight to the point.
I like it.
Me too.
Sure.
I think so too.
Then let's go with that.
Okay.
Let's shout out
for our new group name!
Okay.
Come on.
Yibei will win!
[This retreat]
[has changed everyone a lot.]
[Now the basketball club]
[is truly formed.]
[I don't even have the energy to take a photo.]
Let's go.
Gu Chenyang,
are you hungry?
Mom, I'm back.
Mom.
My son is back.
Welcome home.
Your dad has been asking about you.
Luckily, I got the news
that your middle school
is holding Olympiad training.
I told him
you were working as a teaching assistant.
I even retouched
a few photos for him.
Thank you, mom.
Mom, what are you writing this afternoon?
Your school
is having a reading week, right?
I have to speak at the PTA meeting.
I'm writing my speech.
You've worked hard, mom.
Why are you so grumpy?
Don't be so polite to your mom.
Am I really so grumpy?
I shouldn't have said grumpy.
You should be composed and considerate.
Besides,
who says kids
have to be carefree
and giggly?
Smile.
You look so pretty.
This camp
is really something.
When did you ever
care about this?
It's okay.
No.
I have to write
a long review for them.
Let me take a picture.
Mom.
Don't be shy
with me.
Then stand a bit farther away.
Right.
Turn on the beauty camera.
You're handsome even without it.
Give me a peace sign.
And show your pearly whites.
So good-looking.
Help me out here.
How should I write this review?
Rehabilitation training.
The base you went to
is very professional.
Many professional athletes
go there for rehabilitation.
Is that okay?
Mom, I haven't eaten since I got back.
Oh right.
I'm so forgetful.
Wait a minute.
I'll go prepare it right away.
How about spaghetti?
Okay.
Zhou Yang,
I heard that the Basketball Club
went out for team building during the National Day holiday.
It wasn't team building.
We went out for joint training.
Joint training?
Yes.
It's good to be positive.
But you are the President of the Student Union.
You should keep a balance.
You can't be led astray.
Do you know?
Do you mean
they are too hard
in training?
During the training,
they get up at six o'clock every day to train.
Except for eating and sleeping,
they are playing basketball.
If this is called going astray,
then I think
other clubs
should be led.
All right, all right.
It's good to be flexible.
Then this plan of the arts festival...
Plan of the arts festival.
Then go on
with this plan.
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
Anything else?
No.
Goodbye, sir.
Go ahead.
Zhou Yang.
What's up?
Nothing.
I just want to know
why Fu Binyan
quitted the team.
I don't know
the details.
I didn't go to the competition
because of something urgent.
Soon after, I heard that Fu Binyan
had a bad cold.
I asked him about it,
but he didn't say much.
Later,
at the beginning of the new term,
he said he would
never play basketball again.
I see.
You...
Why are you suddenly interested in this?
Nothing. I just want to know.
Why are you laughing?
I have something to tell you.
I met Fu Binyan
in the bathroom.
I invited him to come and play later.
He agreed.
No, he refused.
Then why are you laughing so happily?
He was very nice today.
Come on, you ask me.
Do you want to
go to the basketball club later?
No, I have something to do.
He never used to be like this.
Yeah.
I also think
his attitude has improved recently.
He even helped me
fix my game console last time.
Next time I see him,
I must have dinner with him.
Yes, we must treat him to dinner.
Last time in the infirmary,
if it weren't for him comforting me,
I might have really quit the club.
Infirmary?
Yes.
It was during the training camp.
Enough.
Instead of discussing others here,
you'd better go to training quickly.
Let's go.
Hello, mom.
I'm fine.
I just took a walk.
I walked a little fast.
Don't worry.
You still dare to play basketball?
Why not?
Can people with heart disease play basketball?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You went to the training base
for rehabilitation training, right?
I looked it up.
It's the most
professional rehab center in Yibei,
specializing in cardiopulmonary and neurological rehab.
Zhou Yang said you left the team
because of a severe cold.
Cold
is one of the triggers
for immune-mediated heart disease.
Gu Chenyang,
you don't have time to study tactics,
but you have time
to study my medical records?
Don't tell anyone.
Okay.
Wait.
There are many ways to
get back on the court,
not just by playing basketball.
Tomorrow is our first game
of the group stage.
If you can come,
our team will welcome you.
This is
the live broadcast of Group A
of the Xuhai Competition Area
of the National High School Boys Basketball League.
Today's opponents
are Yibei Middle School Basketball Team
and Wenshan No.6 Middle School Basketball Team.
The current score is seven to three.
[Yibei Middle School is temporarily in the lead.]
Nice pass!
Go Yibei!
[Lin Qingyuan,]
[No. 77 from Yibei Middle School,]
[is really on fire today.]
One, one!
No. 7 from the blue team
committed a foul.
Two points and one free throw.
Yibei, keep it up!
I can't do this anymore.
[Wenshan starts to closely guard Lin Qingyuan,]
[but]
[Yibei's firepower]
[is still too strong.]
[Gu Chenyang, Zhou Yang, and Li Haoyu,]
[they're scoring from all sides.]
[Wenshan will have to come up with more.]
[No. 18 Xu Anbo]
[also stepped up,]
[reviving the team's offense.]
[No. 50 Li Haoyu is also playing better.]
[He's playing very steadily today,]
[with few mistakes.]
[Of course, Wenshan hasn't given up yet.]
Wenshan!
Defense!
Wenshan, keep it up!
We've got the rebound!
Come on!
Yibei, keep it up!
[Students, it's crunch time.]
[Yibei Middle School]
[has built up a lead]
[in the first half.]
[But Wenshan No. 6 Middle School]
[has shown remarkable resilience,]
[chasing after the score.]
Defense!
[Now both teams]
[are back to the same starting line.]
[The score is 57 to 57.]
[The last 30 seconds.]
[Let's hold our breath]
[and focus on the game.]
It's intercepted.
Li Haoyu intercepted it.
[Let's congratulate]
[Yibei High School Basketball Team]
[on their first victory.]
[This brand new team]
[has announced their arrival]
[with a team victory.]
[The story of this team]
[has just begun.]
Let's take a photo together.
It's so memorable.
Okay.
Awesome.
The last shot was so cool.
I'm proud of you.
I never thought
I could do it.
Captain,
I did well today, right?
Look at me.
Three, two...
Wait.
You should be in the photo too.
It's not a group photo without you.
I'll take it.
Thank you, coach.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Yibei
will win!
Why not choose this one?
Isn't this a pretty good shot?
You call this good?
This is the highlight of my life?
This is it?
This must be
the "submarine" who picked this picture.
Otherwise, why are we two
like we're meme characters?
Director Qian.
Hello, Director Qian.
You guys are really good at basketball.
You've shown the spirit
of Yibei Middle School.
But,
just being good at basketball
isn't enough.
You need to excel in all areas,
especially the two of you.
Show improvement in your next exam,
and I'll put you
on the honor roll again.
No need.
No, no,
we'll keep working hard.
That rhymes!
See you, sir.
Okay, keep going.
I have confidence in you.
Keep it up
and make more achievements.
Good.
Well done.
You are amazing.
This ball is really good.
You just won a game.
Is it worth being so happy for so long?
The provincial tournament
is a round-robin
of four teams.
You've only won one game
against Wenshan No. 6 Middle School,
a team that just formed last year
and isn't very strong.
Besides, they brought in
three freshmen
in the game,
clearly just training them.
Your group
has two teams left.
Fanghe No.3 Middle School was in the top eight last year.
They have the highest average number of fouls.
They like physical confrontation.
Then there's the Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education.
They were the champion last year.
They are especially good at fast breaks.
They have the highest half-court score.
Your tough battle hasn't even started yet.
Well,
Senior Fu Da,
do you come here
just to
beat us?
Do you think I want to come here?
Director Qian asked you
to be all-round,
so I was sent here.
That means you are
spying on us.
You can understand it in this way.
We should play basketball
and study at the same time.
It's good that you are here.
We are in trouble again.
Chi Jia, you say it.
I'll be short.
The cost of the National Day training camp
exceeds the budget.
Our club
is running out of money.
What?
How much do we need? I'll pay.
No.
That will change the nature of the club.
But there's a way.
You mean the Arts Festival?
There's a group talent competition
at the Arts Festival at the end of this month.
The first place will get a prize.
You should have told us earlier.
Talent competition?
Leave it to me.
Don't worry.
Good.
Dad.
I know. I'll handle it.
Wait for me.
You're back.
Why are you home today?
The noodles at the restaurant near school
are super delicious.
Would you like to try some?
I have some work to do at the office.
I'll skip the meal for now.
Stir-fried rice noodles?
I can make them for you.
Okay.
Have something nice.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
Awesome.
If you add another zero to my bonus,
I could even afford a Manchu-Han Imperial Feast.
Got it, I'll handle it.
Wait for me.
Then I guess
I'll just enjoy the feast myself.
Yummy.
Pulsar Band
is going to perform at the Arts Festival.
Join us? Join us? Join us?
Yu, spare me.
My mom's making me memorize vocabulary.
I have to go.
I won't go.
I was caught going to the internet bar with you last time.
My legs were almost broken.
I need to be a new person.
A new person?
You are still
the same.
Brother Yu, I dare not.
A bunch of wimps.
Rock and roll!
Awesome!
Now the game has come to
the final moment.
Li Haoyu
faced a three-man defense.
He turned,
jumped,
and layup.
The ball went in, awesome!
Boring.
Tell me.
Fu Binyan,
is there something
you haven't told me?
Why do you ask?
No reason.
I just have a feeling.
Then you're wrong this time.
Hurry up.
Pulsar Band is recruiting members.
Good pay. PM me if interested.
You again?
We're a team.
It's only right.
Why are you in my space?
We're a team.
The band's
our concern.
Exactly.
There's strength in numbers.
You're the drummer,
Gu Chenyang's on keyboards,
and Lin Qingyuan can play bass.
We're just missing
a guitarist,
and we've already found
the best candidate for you.
Who is it?
How's their skill level?
Just go and listen for yourself.
They're pretty good!
Where did you find them?